# Vitaly Bolychev

+7 921 320 2445

vitaly.bolychev@gmail.com

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **PROFILE INFO**

I have 9-year experience working on financial, social, and government projects for hundreds of thousands customers. I successfully apply microservices approach. I usually ask my team about our performance and efficiency for business. I try to make every solution as much reasonable as possible and after that learn from the result along with my team.

### **SKILLS**

- Focus on efficiency
- Agile processes
- · Microservices architecture
- · Domain-Driven Design
- Network protocols
- · Database optimisation
- · Distributed systems
- Go
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- Kafka
- Docker

# **SOCIALS**

- @VitalyBolychev
- @ @vitalybolychev

## **LANGUAGES**

- English Intermediate
- Russian Native

#### REFERENCES

References are available on request

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Senior Software Engineer**

Mail.ru Group

August 2020 - Present

I participate in development of electronic bulletin board service called Youla. As part of BtoB team I developed integrations with a number of external services such as Vkontakte. Also as part of vehicles team I help to develop appropriate domain in Youla.

## **Senior Software Engineer**

Space307

January 2019 - August 2020

I had developed backend for e-wallet internet application using microservice architecture. Me and my team worked on payment processing as well as on general product features like a notification system. Now I'm working on trading platform which serves more than 15 000 clients online in peaks every day. I help to build system which carries on flexible trading conditions for each user depending on its trading experience.

### **Senior Software Engineer**

Devim

June 2016 - January 2019

I focused on development for financial projects. I helped the company to develop its own scalable, reliable microservice architecture. Participated in designing, implementing and releasing CRM system for country-wide financial company.

#### **EDUCATION**

St. Petersburg State Electrotechnical University "LETI" Master's degree in Computer security